Contact

johnguarra2@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/john-cloedguarra-92358417a (LinkedIn) johncloed.github.io/portfolio/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

WordPress

Elementor

Google Ads

Certifications

Google Ads - Measurement Certification

HubSpot Marketing Software

Google Ads Search Certification

Google Analytics Individual Qualification

John Cloed Guarra

Web Developer, Social Media Manager, and Ads Expert.

Daet, Bicol Region, Philippines

Summary

Technical skills

- HTML
- · CSS, CSS3
- ¡Query
- PHP
- MySQL
- Proficient in Microsoft Office products

Certified Google Ads and Facebook Ads specialist who has 3+ years of experience and managed different campaigns for different types of businesses. Help in achieving clients' digital and social media marketing goals, allowing to have a better understanding of how their business performs and generate outstanding results and progress.

Expertise includes:

- Digital marketing
- Google ads/PPC
- Facebook and Instagram Ads
- Social media Manager
- Certified HubSpot Marketing Software Expert
- Certified Canva Designer
- Google Analytics
- Website design and development
- Content Creation
- Video Editing

Experience

Fiverr
Graphic Designer
February 2021 - Present (2 years)
Tel Aviv, Israel

Upwork

3 years 8 months

Website Developer, Digital Marketer and Data Entry Assistant August 2020 - Present (2 years 6 months)

San Francisco, California, United States

Digital Marketing Specialist June 2019 - Present (3 years 8 months)

RADSEO

Wordpress Developer July 2022 - January 2023 (7 months) Arizona, United States

Education

Camarines Norte State College
Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (2020 - 2022)

Microsystem College Foundation Inc.

Grade 12, Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2018 - 2020)